reduceimages.com 2011-05-27

# Privacy Policy - www.reduceimages.com

Through our privacy policy we tell you our terms and conditions of use:

Using this site implies the acceptance without restrains of all the conditions included in this legal advice, if you don't agree with this terms and conditions, you must not use this site.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy in any moment. Your continuous use of any portion of this site after the notification of that modifications will imply your acceptance of those changes.

### Cookies.

This site uses cookies. Cookies are small data files that generate on your computer, which send information without giving any reference that allow to deduce your personal information.

You can configure your browser to notify and reject the instalation of the cookies sent by this site, while still being able to access the contents of this site. Despite of that, we don't responsabilize of malfunctioning of this site if you deactivate cookies.

### Web Beacons

The same as cookies, this site can also contain web beacons, grapchic files that allow to count users that access the site or derermined cookies of it, this way we can offer you an even more personalized experience.

### 3rd Party Actions

You may also find on this site pages, promotions, microsites, virtual shopping sites, surveys, sponsors, advertisers, contractors and/or partners and comercial services, in addition to other services that can request information, which this site can reveal information provided by you.

Information provided to 3rd party sites is subscribed to the privacy policies or information responsability legends shown on that sites and will not be subjected to this privacy policy. Because of that we widely recommend to users to review in detail the privacy policies shown on any external site.

Privacy Policy of the Ads on this site:

* Google Adsense: http://www.google.com/intl/es_ALL/privacypolicy.html

We study the preferences of our users, their demographic characteristics and traffic patterns and other information as a whole to get a better understanding of our audience composition and what you need. Tracking those preferences of our users help us to offer you the advertising that is more relevant for you.

Privacy Policy of the Source Tracking used on this site:

* Google (Analytics): http://www.google.com/intl/es_ALL/privacypolicy.html

### Personal Information Protection Policy

To use some of the services and contents you will have to previosuly supply some personal information that will only be used for the purpose that they were gathered for.

The type of information that may be requested includes but doesn't limit to: name, e-mail address, birth date, sex, occupation, country, city or personal interests among others, not all the information requested at the moment of using the site is obligatory, only that that we consider convinient.

As a general principle, this site doesn't share or reveal any information gathered except when you authorize it or in the following cases:

a) When it's required by a competent authority and after the correspondant legal process.

b) When this site judges it necessary to respect the terms and conditions of use of this site or to protect the integrity of other users of the site.

You must be concious that if you decide to reveal personal information in a public area of the site, that information can be collected and used by others. We don't control the actions of our visitors and users.

### Responsible Behaviour

All the information you provide must be real. To this effect, you guarantee the authenticity of all the information you enter in any form needed to use the services or contents of this site. On every circumpstances you will be the only responsible of any false or inaccurate information you provide and the damage that it may cause to this site or others.

You promise to act in a responsible way in this site and respect other users.
